[Music]
definitely with this recognition it will
give us
even continuous motivation and
aspiration to continuously invest in our
people especially in their development
in their wellness and mental health
especially
so
that's that's what gonna inspire us the
continuous investment in our people
first of all we i would like to thank
our aspiring ceo viva coburn
for driving and steering not just the
business but the people strategy
together with me
and secondly thank the leaders of
manulife without them
there would be no people engagement and
thirdly the manulifers the fellow
employees of manulife who continuously
deadly being dedicated committed to
deliver our business
[Music]
you